zipscene.com 2018-08-25

# Zipscene Privacy Policy · Zipscene

_Effective June 17, 2013_

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Zipscene LLC, an Ohio limited liability company, (“Zipscene”, “us”, “we” or “our”) collects, protects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of www.zipscene.com, [www.cafezipscene.com](http://www.cafezipscene.com/) (the “Sites”) and any website that we maintain on behalf of our clients (the “Client Sites”). This privacy policy applies to our Sites and our Client Sites and all products and services offered by Zipscene, and describes how we use, share and protect the information that we collect.

Information is at the core of Zipscene’s business. Our programs involve various uses of information, including the storage, exchange, transfer, management, analysis and reporting of such information.  We create engaging digital marketing programs for our clients.  We also collect and use information we and our Clients gather through the Sites and the Client Sites, as well as our Clients’ retail operations to create and facilitate the delivery of ads, promotions and offers tailored to the preferences of the users of the Sites and the Client Sites.  To do this, we gather information  regarding our clients’ customers’ use of the Client Sites and other online and in-store services to create customer profiles, allowing us and our clients to use what is learned to deliver custom content and offers to their customers. We also obtain marketing information (including information about customers) from third parties and may combine all of this information to make it more complete, accurate and useful.

**Commitment to Privacy**

We are committed to maintaining the confidentiality, integrity and security of any personal information under our control.  We use industry-standard security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of such information.

**Consent and Modifications to the Privacy Policy**

By using the Sites and the Client Sites and providing information to Zipscene or through one or more of the Client Sites, you signify your consent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Sites or our Client Sites or provide your information to us.

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time.  In the event this Privacy Policy is modified, we will provide notice of the change by posting the updated Privacy Policy to the www.zipscene.com and [www.cafezipscene.com](http://www.cafezipscene.com/).  You agree that the electronic posting of a modified Privacy Policy to our Sites represents actual notice to you.  Unless otherwise provided in an agreement between you and Zipscene, by using the Sites or the Client Sites after Zipscene posts a modified Privacy Policy, you agree to accept those changes, whether or not you have reviewed them, and such acceptance shall be deemed legally conclusive.  If at any time you choose not to accept the terms of this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Sites or the Client Sites or enter information about yourself or your business.

**Information We Collect**

_Non-Personal Information_. We may collect technical, non-personal identification information about our users and our clients’ customers whenever they interact with our Site or the Client Sites that use our services and technology.  Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about your means of connection to the site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

_Personal Information of our Sites’ Users_. We may collect personal identification information from users of our Sites in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when users visit our Sites, register on our Sites, purchase a product, subscribe to a newsletter, apply for a job, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Sites.  We also collect information about your activity on the Sites and the Client Sites, including pages viewed, items clicked, and dates and times of visits.  You may visit our Sites anonymously except that it may prevent you from engaging in certain site-related activities.

_Personal Information of our Clients’ Users obtained through Client Sites_.  We collect personal information of Customers through our Clients’ marketing programs, such as your name, address, email address, phone number, and purchase and order history (including your credit card information, billing and/or shipping information).  We rely upon the instructions of our clients with respect to a customer’s preferences or opt-in/opt-out choices.  If you would like to be removed from our mailing lists, update your information, or change your preferences about the information you receive from us, please contact us directly by emailing us at [privacy@zipscene.com](mailto:privacy@zipscene.com).

_Personal Information collected from Third Parties_. We collect personal information about our clients’ customers and other individuals from other sources and add it to our database of user account information. Examples of this information may include, but is not limited to, name, address, email address, phone number, purchase or redemption information, order history, and page-view and activity data information.  When we associate information that we obtain from third parties with personal information that we have collected under this policy, we will treat the acquired information like the information that we collected ourselves.

**How We Use The Information We Collect**

We use the information we collect about you to administer our Sites and our Client Sites and to  provide you with the information, services or products that you request. We combine the data that we receive from our clients’ customers with other sources to create customer profiles. We use profile data to improve the customer experience by providing you with custom marketing messages and offers on behalf of our clients.  We also share such aggregated and de-individualized profile data with third parties (in a form that will not allow you to be identified) for market research and other purposes.

**To Whom We May Disclose The Information We Collect**

We take reasonable precautions to be sure that nonaffiliated third parties and affiliates to whom we disclose your personally identifiable information are aware of our privacy policy and will treat the information in a similarly responsible manner. Our contracts and written agreements with nonaffiliated third parties that receive information from us about you prevent further transfer of the information.  We will not disclose your personal information to third parties except to provide you with the product or service you request, or under the circumstances described in this policy.

_Agents & Contractors_. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Sites and the Client Sites or to administer activities on our behalf. Our contractors sometimes have access to your personal information in the course of assisting in operating our business and providing products or services to you. These contractors include vendors and suppliers that provide us with technology, services, and/or content for the operation and maintenance of our site. Contractors have an obligation under their contracts with us to keep your information confidential and to comply with our privacy and security policies.

_Marketing Purposes_.  We share aggregated and de-individualized data with third parties (in a form that will not allow you to be identified) for market research and other purposes.  We may also share your personal information with third parties for marketing purposes, provided that you have opted-in to receive such offers or messages.

_Aggregated non-personal information_. We may share aggregated non-personal information about you and de-identified individual data and profiles with third parties. This is information that is combined with the non-personal information of other users and does not allow you to be identified or contacted. Depending on the circumstances, we may or may not charge third parties for this aggregated information. We also may not limit the third parties’ use of the aggregated information or de-identified individual data.

_Changes in our Company Structure._ We may choose to sell all or a portion of our assets. In such a transaction, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if Zipscene, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Zipscene goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information could be transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and you consent that any acquirer of Zipscene may continue to use your personal and non-personal information pursuant to the terms set forth in this policy.

_Disclosure for Legal Reasons_. We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that it is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Zipscene, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Sites and our Client Sites each may use “cookies” to enhance user experience. Cookies are unique identifiers that we transfer to a user’s device to enable our systems to recognize the device and to provide certain features of our Sites and our Client Sites to the user. Cookies are also used for record-keeping and sometimes to track information about users. You may choose to set your web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent.  However, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, some parts of our Sites and/or our Client Sites may not function properly. ****

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Sites that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Sites. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites that have a link to our Sites, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act**

Protecting the privacy of children is especially important. For that reason, we do not collect or maintain information on our Sites or our Client Sites from those we know are under age 13, and no part of our Sites is structured to attract anyone under 13.  If the parent or guardian of a child under 13 believes that the child has provided us with any information through any of the Sites or the Client Sites, the parent or guardian of that child should contact us if they want this information deleted from our files. If we obtain knowledge from any source that Zipscene has information about a child under 13 in retrievable form in its files, we will delete that information from our existing files.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our Sites may make any changes to their information at any time by contacting us directly: [privacy@zipscene.com](mailto:privacy@zipscene.com).

**Contacting us**

If your personal information changes, we invite you to correct or update your information as soon as possible. You can request changes or access to your information by emailing [privacy@zipscene.com](mailto:privacy@zipscene.com).  If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of our Sites, or your dealings with our Client Sites, please contact us at:

Zipscene

http://www.zipscene.com

privacy@zipscene.com
